[Music]
Hey puppy, eat sweets, understand
[Music] Yes,
who is this sweet?
Hey, today that Kunna Munna is passing the exam and
two government exams are passing, hey, wow,
this is a great devotee
[Music]
Hey Baba, thank you, I bless you all
Baba, daughter-in-law, brother, sister-in-law, I am doing engineering, I am doing
engineering, I need 10 lakh rupees,
ok, if you worry, I am busy, if you don't want to arrange money, I will do it, I will study, hey,
who will
sell it, hey, this is the
solution, Nathila, pass the engineer, you will
deposit it, [Music]
Papa, this is my mind, study, and become an
engineer [Music]
[Music]
Who is this, three people are not depositing money, I am also
filling up the form, last date Baba, if the
money is not deposited, then I will not be able to appear for the exam,
Baba, you are busy, it is
very important, Madan, you are doing engineering, I need to make arrangements,
O grandmother,
hey, no brother, Dada Jogi,
who will sell it
Call me grandma, there is
no solution for it [Music] There is no solution for it [Music] The
money is worthless When the money is worthless, then the
inconvenience will be resolved.
Ji ji, I am not here
even today, you should get up, you have come and
see, the
work is for the
week, you should call me, if you get up then the
work will be done, you will
definitely do it on
Diwali day,
laugh at the happiness of the house, [Music] There is no
split in the house from today, the mind said, I feel happy at home
[Music]
Who is this, I did not come empty handed, I did
not even like the food, I also bought the medicine and the shop
said the rest of the money, if you are not happy then
feel sad, do
n't go to sleep because of hunger
[Music]
Oh God, I have
not come for two years, I am angry, Lord, I am tolerant, Oh
grandma,
[Laughter]
Lord,
grandma, don't
even give me the money, she did not say the doctor, there is
delay in getting the news, Oh
grandma,
see, if
you are fine then run away, get the treatment done
[Music]
[Music] [Music
]
[Music]
Uncle, what are you saying, you are good [Music]
Baba, Tiku se ko Daki ji [Music]
[Music] [Music
]
Dhan re listen, you are leaving, you are a little bit hey, hey
everyone is of high standard [Music]
Mundiya Bapa go
[Music] go for
normal, if you give me money, the car is for seven
years, mother hey
I
also need money, go, go
fast
hey
baba, you are
not sitting on anyone, you are right, Bokaso, the house is full of people
[Music] I do
n't want to live, I don't want to live, who is that dancer, I have to give up
everything, I have to give up everything [
Music] I don't want to go to school, I am not going to go to
school, I am going ...
Thank you very much God, please do good, thank you for the
inconvenience,
we are doing our duty,
Grandma, please hurry up, please hurry up, please
see, who is the news
[Music] Munna has committed a
crime, the stick must be taken care of, hey look, look
Munna, please
forgive your mother and your father, you have committed a
mistake, today you will have to face the punishment, please
hurry up, please forgive me,
everything is fine,
everything is bad, don't look at me,
Grandma, give me 400 rupees,
brother, please forgive me by mistake, I don't
mean that the
earthly priceless sister-in-law, the natural gem, I have
sacrificed the pain,
I have forgiven you, Grandma, I have
forgiven you by mistake, human,
hey look, leave the
basic intelligence, Grandma, say sorry, sorry, sorry to
everyone
[Music]